freshmonk.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy describes how FreshMonk collects and uses the personal information you provide on www.freshmonk.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. 

#### **Collection and Use of Personal Information**

We collect the following personal information from you:

  1. Contact information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number
  2. Billing information such as name and billing address

As is true of most websites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system. We use this information to: 

  1. Fulfill your order
  2. Send you an order confirmation
  3. Send you requested product or service information
  4. Send product updates or warranty information
  5. Respond to customer service requests
  6. Administer your account
  7. Respond to your questions and concerns

#### **Operational Use.**

We may use your information for suggesting products and promotional offers and schemes. You may update your profiling information at any time on the profile page. You acknowledge and agree such update is for Your interests and for improving personalization and efficiency of our service. 

#### **Information Sharing**

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

If you participate in a white-labeled enterprise campaign (identified by the enterprise having their logo in the top left of the campaign, as opposed to the FreshMonk logo) we may share your name, email address and order breakdown of size and quantity with the enterprise customers for the purposes of continued contact. This information is encrypted on the FreshMonk database and is only decrypted to send to the enterprise client securely. After this has been completed, the plain-text data is purged from the FreshMonk server. To opt out of this marketing, please contact the white-labeled enterprise customer.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us. We may also disclose your personal information:

  1. As required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  2. When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request
  3. If FreshMonk is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information
  4. To any other third party with your prior consent to do so

#### **Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We also encrypt customer information in our database so that customers name and address is never stored in plain text. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. Please contact us, if you have any questions about security on our website.

We provide two means for you to make a purchase on our site. You can either use our order form or a third party payment option. If you use our shopping cart, the transmission of sensitive information collected on our order form is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and is processed by PayUMoney, MobiKwik or PayTM. If you choose to use a third party payment option, such as PayPal, to pay for your order, its privacy policy and security practices will apply to your information. We encourage you to read that privacy policy before providing your information.

#### **Cookies and other tracking technologies**

We may use cookies, for example, to keep track of your preferences and profile information. Cookies are also used to collect general usage and volume statistical information that does not include personal information. We use another company to place cookies on your computer to collect non-personal information to compile aggregated statistics for us about visitors to our site.

We use local shared objects, also known as Flash cookies, to store your preferences such as volume control or high game score, or display content based upon what you view on our site to personalize your visit. Third parties, with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your web browsing activity, use Flash cookies to collect and store information. Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how data is stored. Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies click [here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html#117118)

#### **Links to Other Websites**

Our site includes links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of FreshMonk. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website you visit.

#### **Analytics Data Gathering**

We use third party analytics tools, such as Google Analytics to measure traffic and website usage. One feature we use in Google Analytics is non-personally identifiable 3rd-party audience data (such as age, gender, and interests), which we use to improve our service.

#### **Data Retention**

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. Please contact us if you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

#### **Deletion / Deactivation**

If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, or delete it by making the change on our member information page or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.

#### **Social Media Features and Widgets**

Our website includes social media features, such as the Facebook like button and widgets. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

#### **Facebook Connect or Open ID**

You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

#### **Testimonials**

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [support@freshmonk.com](mailto:support@freshmonk.com)

#### **Notification of Privacy Policy Changes**

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

#### **Contact Information:**

FreshMonk  
91 Design Labs Pte Ltd.  
Email: [support@freshmonk.com](mailto:support@freshmonk.com)  
Telephone: +91-9739062226br>

_Corporate Address:_   
10 Anson Road  
#26-04, International Plaza  
Singapore 079903  

_Updated January 1st, 2015_
